<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="1.0">
<channel>
<title>Multihack for Counter Strike Global Offensive</title>
<link>https://csgo.cheatsformacs.com/api/update.xml</link>
<description>Most recent changes</description>
<language>en</language>
<item>
<title>Version 6.3.4</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<ul> <b>Change log</b><br> <br> <b>Version 6.3.4</b> <li>During settings reset, license will be now saved to your clipboard.</li> <br> <b>Version 6.3.3</b> <li>Added possibility to reset cheat settings to default</li> <li>Added MOUSE1 (fire) as aimbot activation hotkey. With legit settings it makes aimbot fairly legit. In order to use, DO NOT enable aimbot by keyboard shortcut or toggle, setting appropriate MOUSE1-MOUSE5 will activate it on mouse click.</li> <br> <b>Version 6.3.2</b> <li>Improved error messages</li> <br> <b>Version 6.3.1</b> <li>Fixed issue with update alerts</li> <br> <b>Version 6.3.0</b> <li>Fixed update behaviour</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.9</b> <li>Added "Free for all" mode which makes cheat consider all players as enemies. Useful for custom servers with <b>mp_teammates_are_enemies</b> enabled</li> <li>Fixed performance bottleneck</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.8</b> <li>Fixed issue with entering license key</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.7</b> <li>Fixed issue with aimbot randomly locking down on air</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.6</b> <li>Minor Improvements</li> <li>Auto-close fix before entering license</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.5</b> <li>Minor Improvements</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.4</b> <li>Fixed recent issues after game update. (Sorry for delay) </li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.3</b> <li>General improvements</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.2</b> <li>Fixed issue "ERROR GETTING FILE" for some users.</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.1</b> <li>Implemented feature to prevent cheat to start when there is new game update, to additionally, manually run some tests and make sure cheat is safe and bug free</li> <br> <b>Version 6.2.0</b> <li>Fixed aimbot and norecoil</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.9</b> <li>Fixed bug due recent game update</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.8</b> <li>Improved detection of current game state which will avoid weird crashes and weird behaviours</li> <li>Fixed issue when cheat did not enabled at all when users rushed with toggling features before joining team or game</li> <li>Improved status bar</li> <li>Fixed issue with enabling/disabling visibility check for wallhack/esp</li> <li>Improved hints and how to use</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.7</b> <li>Fixed issue when leaving game to main menu and then rejoining game broke wallhack and aimbot</li> <li>Fixed issue when Aimbot wasn't dropping target after gone invisible</li> <li>Improved Bhop</li> <li>Fixed wallhack visibility check issue after changing map / server</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.6</b> <li>Fixed rare crash when map has been analysed when wasn’t fully loaded</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.5</b> <li>Fixed Aimbot Helper key issue forcing aimbot to rage sometimes</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.4</b> <li>Fixed another 2 quite rare cases of csgohack.app crash</li> <li>Fixed Aimbot target evaluation (it has been broken from initial release of revised aimbot version 6.0.0, targets were chosen randomly ignoring selected mode, now it’s fixed)</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.3</b> <li>Fixed segmentation fault crash caused due improper hotkeys/toggles activation before full initialisation</li> <li>Fixed bug when Wallhack/ESP and aimbot suddenly stopped working during game</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.2</b> <li>Fixed Aimbot Semi-Auto / Semi issue</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.1</b> <li>Fixed updater issue</li> <br> <b>Version 6.1.0</b> <li>Added Triggerbot knife trick for scoped rifle. For example - AWP > Knife > AWP</li> <br> <b>Version 6.0.3</b> <li>Improved error reporting</li> <br> <b>Version 6.0.2</b> <li>Fixed Aimbot minimum movement factor</li> <br> <b>Version 6.0.1</b> <li>Fixed Aimbot minimum fov</li> <br> <b>Version 6.0.0</b> <li>Completely rewritten cheat engine (improved overall performance)</li> <li>Fixed random crashes during gameplay</li> <li>Improved Norecoil</li> <li>Completely rewritten and improved Aimbot</li> <li>Aimbot Legit & Rage mode pre-set</li> <li>Multiple new Aimbot features</li> <li>Improved ESP/Wallhack</li> <li>ESP/Wallhack for weapons</li> <li>ESP/Wallhack if player/object is visible or not</li> <li>Performance/Cpu usage adjustment possibility</li> <br> <b>Version 5.2.5</b> <li>Fixed Trigger bot & Slow aim</li> <br> <b>Version 5.2.4</b> <li>Fixed issue with "Set License" and "How to use" buttons.</li> <br> <b>Version 5.2.3</b> <li>Fixed Slow Aim</li> <li>Fixed other minor issues reported by users</li> <br> <b>Version 5.2.2</b> <li>Minor Fix</li> <br> <b>Version 5.2.1</b> <li>Added license lock/unlock button to let change license easily</li> <li>General Improvements</li> <br> <b>Version 5.2.0</b> <li>Added toggle buttons for those with problems with shortcuts usage</li> <li>Fixed slowaim</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.9</b> <li>Compatibility fix 10.11/10.12</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.8</b> <li>Backward compatibility fix</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.7</b> <li>Minor fixes</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.6</b> <li>Minor improvements</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.5</b> <li>Fixed annoying issue when triggerbot was interrupting manual shooting, now triggerbot will only start shooting when Mouse1 (attack button) is not being pressed.</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.4</b> <li>Fixed compatibility issue with new version of CSGO which caused minor issues</li> <li>Fixed issue with slow aim which existed from beginning for some users</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.3</b> <li>Fixed issue with aimbot locking down on target killed in previous round</li> <li>Fixed issue with wallhack randomly stop working</li> <li>Most likely fixed random game crash for some users</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.2</b> <li>Minor issues fix</li> <li>Improved stability</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.1</b> <li>Fixed backward compatibility with macOS before Yosemite (10.7,10.8)</li> <li>Fixed few minor issues</li> <br> <b>Version 5.1.0</b> <li>Added option to triggerbot to allow auto ducking when enabled</li> <li>Added option to triggerbot to do not attack when holding c4,knife,grenades</li> <li>Added option to triggerbot to do not shot when holding sniper weapons unscoped</li> <li>Added Slow Aim function - when enabled your mouse will extremely slow down on enemy, after enemy is killed or crosshair moved out of enemy then speed will return to your default one. Do not change mouse senstivity while using cheat!</li> <li>Fixed issue with no recoil with triggerbot</li> <li>Fixed issue with message alert locking down cheat</li> <li>General cheat improvements</li> <br> <b>Version 4.1.3</b> <li>Fixed last no-recoil issue, it's working flawlessly now - can't go better than this with real recoil reduction since spread seed is generated by servers</li> <li>Fixed error and status messages</li> <br> <b>Version 4.1.2</b> <li>Fixed issue with aimbot when enemy is ducking</li> <li>Fixed default movement factor for aimbot, now by default it's working smoothly</li> <li>Changed way of handling key detection which if more optimised (notify us if something does not work properly)</li> <li>Improved performance, reduced cpu usage by 75%</li> <br> <b>Version 4.1.1</b> <li>Minor issue fix</li> <br> <b>Version 4.1.0</b> <li>Fixed issue with wallhack/esp when cheat started before game, now it should work. You can now start cheat entirely before starting game or just start after like before</li> <li>Improved Triggerbot - Fixed issues for some users, ex. randomly looking down</li> <li>Improved Auto-Bhop - Peformance improvements </li> <li>Added Enable-All feature - Will enable all features except Aimbot (CMD+L)</li> <li>Added Auto-Duck - Added automatic ducking when shooting to improve accuracy (CMD+>)</li> <br> <b>Version 4.0.3</b> <li>Minor issues fix</li> <li>Now cheat can be started before game is started!</li> <li>After CS:GO update, usually we can fix everything remotely but sometimes it may require update like this one</li> <br> <b>Version 4.0.2</b> <li>Minor issues fix</li> <br> <b>Version 4.0.1</b> <li>Spelling fix</li> <br> <b>Version 4.0</b> <li>Improved memory & cache cleaner</li> <li>Fixed broken aimbot distance activation feature</li> <li>Improved overall preformance & issues with premissions on some older macOS</li> <li>Added feature to detect new CS:GO version with automatic notification for us</li> <li>Improved feature to detect changes in VAC to prevent getting banned while they change something</li> <li>Fixed random lags</li> <br> <b>Version 3.3</b> <li>Added cache & memory cleaner (Fix for getting lags after playing few games)</li> <br> <b>Version 3.2</b> <li>Added aimbot activation point on distance between enemy and your current mouse position, set this value experimentally - "15" will activate on distance similar to 2 x character width. With this and Hotkey you can achieve overwatch undetect ability with Silent Aimbot feature</li> <br> <b>Version 3.1</b> <li>Added aimbot movement factor</li> <li>Fixed wh/esp issue with random bodies</li> <li>Improved aimbot</li> <li>Other minor performance improvements</li> <br> <b>Version 3.0</b> <li>Added Aimbot</li> <li>Rage Aimbot</li> <li>Aim Helper with custom hotkey</li> <li>No Recoil - Reversed, slightly reduced</li> <br> <b>Version 2.3</b> <li>Fixed issue with wallhack and esp while using long interval with trigger bot</li> <li>Along with shooting interval now you can set up each one shoot lenght</li> <li>Fixed performance issue</li> <li>Added VAC changes detector to prevent getting banned when Valve decide to do something about macOS & Linux</li> <br>Current Multihack features appears to be stable so we have started working on:<br> <li>Rage Aimbot (obvious)</li> <li>Soft Aimbot - Aim helper (hardly noticeable even on overwatch)</li> <br> <b>Version 2.2</b> <li>Fixed automatic check for updates</li> <br> <b>Version 2.1</b> <li>Added more options to Wallhack & ESP</li> <li>Possibility to set custom colors</li> <li>Possibility to glow your team members</li> <li>Now all previously set values are stored on your computer</li> <br> <b>Version 2.0</b> <li>Improved cheat performance like x10</li> <li>No more lags</li> <li>Adjustable Trigger Bot Shooting Interval</li> <li>Adjusted BHOP intervals, now it's perfect</li> <li>Added Self-Updater to make updates as easy as one click</li> <br> <b>Version 1.1</b> <li>Added No Flash</li> <li>Added Trigger Bot</li> <li>Added Auto Bhop</li> <br> <b>Version 1.0</b> <li>Initial Release</li> </ul>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>2 feb 2017 03:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://csgo.cheatsformacs.com/download/csgo_hack.zip" sparkle:version="6.3.4" length="297758" type="application/octet-stream"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
